# HIKARI KOBE

# Front-End Developer



h.kobe712@gmail.com

◆ Vancouver, BC



https://github.com/Hikari7 | linkedin.com/in/hikari-kobe-106054242

#### SUMMARY

A Front-End Developer who is passionate about creating web applications in JavaScript and React. I am highly motivated and consistently learn and improve my skills. I have strong communication skills as I have worked a customer service as technical support specialist for 3 years of experience.

#### SKILLS

ReactJS | Redux | JavaScript (ES6) | CSS3( Sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS ) | GSAP HTML5 | Git | Firebase | Figma

#### **PROJECTS**

### Sleep tight

A web app only plays BGM-related relaxing sounds fetched by Youtube Data API. Well designed the minimized styling to help the user to focus on sleeping.

React, GSAP, Tailwind CSS, Youtube Data API v3

## **Oatmeal EC Website**

An EC website was made with vanilla JavaScript and used the browser's local strage. JavaScript (ES6), SASS

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Barista, Starbucks | Vancouver, BC | 2022.8 - Present

• Collaborating with a team of 20 to handle 800 + customers a day.

Technical Support Specialist / Trainer, Japan Concentrix k.k | Japan | 2019.4 - 2022.2

- Offered various customer technical support ranging from supporting the launch of a hotel property's website on the online travel agency site and to game player technical support.
- Trained more than 130 employees successfully and received the Best Employee of the Quarter Award for my training achievements.

#### **EDUCATION**

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada | Vancouver, BC | 2022.5 - Present

- · Web Development Diploma
- Learned core skills related to a front-end developer: JavaScript(ES6), ReactJS, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Git, etc

Seinan Gakuin University | Japan | 2014.4 - 2018.3

Bachelor of Intercultual studies